Hello friends, ICICI LBT has released its quarter
4 numbers.  So
let's see.  But before that let me tell you
that the company has also announced dividend.  The
company is going to give you dividend of approximately ₹7.  So
let's look at the numbers.  The data is basically
in lakhs.  I am telling you in crores.
So in the last quarter the company had
generated a total income of Rs 6610 crore.  5851 crores last year.
Whereas if we look at it now, Rs 6618
crore is seen going away.  So if we
look at it year after year, then every year or two, there is a tremendous growth of
around 13% in the total income of the company.
And if we look at it on a quarter basis,
almost flat is visible here.  So let's
see what the company's expenses are.
So in the last quarter the company had
spent Rs 639 crore.  Last year it was 5435 crores
whereas now if we look at it, only 672 crores are being seen going away.
So the expense
is okay.  To a large extent, you are seen to be in control.
So let's see what the company's profit is.
So in the last
quarter the company had made a profit of Rs 658 crore.
Last year it was 59 crores whereas if we
look at it now, it is seen that 540 crores are being spent.
So if we look at it year after year, then
year after year
there is an increase of around 8% in the profit of the company
and if we
look at it on quarterly basis then there is a decline of around 15% here.
So you can see the profit increasing year after year.
But on a
quarterly basis, you are seeing a decline here.
So let's
see what the company's EPS is.  So last
quarter the company's EPS was ₹13.25, last
year ₹10.29 whereas if seen now, it is
seen going down to ₹10.97.  So
overall, according to me the company did
not show any special numbers.  Let's see the rest as per the
market numbers.  So that's all for today.  If you
like the video then please like it.
Also, please subscribe to the channel.